const data = 
[
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95047f",
    "correctAnswer": "a synonym for taxonomy",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the phylum Bryozoa",
      "interactions among organisms and the water cycle",
      "a branch of theology concerned with the final events in the history of the world or of mankind"
    ],
    "question": "What is Taxology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3e7cc59eab6f9522b0",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "10",
      "1",
      "0"
    ],
    "question": "How is the binary number '10' expressed as a decimal?",
    "tags": [
      "science",
      "numbers",
      "mathematics",
      "computing"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504ce",
    "correctAnswer": "prehistoric people and human origins",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes",
      "study of refuse and trash",
      "crime"
    ],
    "question": "What is Paleoanthropology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95052a",
    "correctAnswer": "gross and disgusting things",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "crayfish",
      "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions",
      "periodic biological phenomena such as flowering, migration, breeding, etc"
    ],
    "question": "What is Grossology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95051d",
    "correctAnswer": "the history, languages, and cultures of the Indian subcontinent",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "the physiological bases of psychological processes",
      "relationships between humans and animals over time through examination of animal remains at archaeological sites",
      "proper names"
    ],
    "question": "What is Indology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3e7cc59eab6f952261",
    "correctAnswer": "Hyper Text Transfer Protocol",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hard Time Telecommunications Pact",
      "Head To Tail Photons",
      "High Top Transduction Paths"
    ],
    "question": "In computer networking what do the initials HTTP stand for?",
    "tags": [
      "science",
      "computing",
      "the_internet",
      "initials"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f950fda",
    "correctAnswer": "Coca Cola",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dr Pepper",
      "Lucozade",
      "Irn Bru"
    ],
    "question": "Which Significant Did Dr John Pemberton Of Atlanta Georgia Invent In 1886?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "6243341fcfaae40c12961424",
    "correctAnswer": "A Billy",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Macho",
      "A Drone",
      "A Ram"
    ],
    "question": "A male goat is known as what?",
    "tags": [
      "animals",
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95054a",
    "correctAnswer": "The practice of breaking free from restraints",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Schematic layouts",
      "Survival during natural disasters",
      "Volcanoes"
    ],
    "question": "What is escapology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504fe",
    "correctAnswer": "mammals",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "wonders, or monsters",
      "wine and winemaking",
      "mechanical, physical, and biochemical functions of living organisms"
    ],
    "question": "What is Mammalogy the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "624437b1746187c5e7be936c",
    "correctAnswer": "It is used in disinfectants and antiseptics.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "It is used in nuclear reactors, as a neutron moderator.",
      "It is used as oscillators in radios, watches.",
      "It is used for surface purification, bleaching, odour removal and water disinfection."
    ],
    "question": "What is the chemical isopropyl alcohol often used for?",
    "tags": [
      "chemistry",
      "general_knowledge",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95104f",
    "correctAnswer": "Distance",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Time",
      "Pressure",
      "Magnetism"
    ],
    "question": " What does a micron measure?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510b7",
    "correctAnswer": "Bones",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eyes",
      "Arms",
      "Stomach"
    ],
    "question": "In what body part does an osteopath specialise?",
    "tags": [
      "anatomy",
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951107",
    "correctAnswer": "Rattlesnakes",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spiders",
      "Frogs",
      "Beetles"
    ],
    "question": "__________ gather in groups to sleep through the winter. ",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "62433426cfaae40c12961427",
    "correctAnswer": "A Gander",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A Leopardess",
      "A Bitch",
      "A Hembra"
    ],
    "question": "What is the word for a female goose?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510d1",
    "correctAnswer": "Heart",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Soul",
      "Blood",
      "Eyes"
    ],
    "question": "What part of the body does carditis affect?",
    "tags": [
      "medicine",
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504ae",
    "correctAnswer": "alternative method of massage, manipulative therapy|therapy or pressure on certain points of the sole of the feet as a means of relieving nervous tension",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "feces",
      "study of the mouth and its diseases",
      "karyotypes"
    ],
    "question": "What is Reflexology the study of?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3e7cc59eab6f95228b",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "2",
      "50",
      "24"
    ],
    "question": "How many teeth does thr average adult human have?",
    "tags": [
      "biology",
      "anatomy",
      "numbers",
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951052",
    "correctAnswer": "Buck",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Doe",
      "Colt",
      "A Johnny"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these is a name for a male deer?",
    "tags": [
      "science"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510aa",
    "correctAnswer": "Milky way",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Andromeda",
      "Ursa",
      "Orion"
    ],
    "question": "What is the name of the galaxy that includes our solar system?",
    "tags": [
      "science",
      "astronomy",
      "physics",
      "space",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [
      
    ]
  }
]

export { data };